Jobs With Justice records 6369
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Series I. National Jobs With Justice
  - Sarita Gupta Files
    - "Another World is Possible" World Social Forum, 2004 (Box 28, Folder 12)
    - Health Care Report - Waste Not, Want Not, 2004-10 (Box 28, Folder 13)
    - Jobs with Justice Board of Directors, 2005 (Box 28, Folder 14)
    - Jobs with Justice History, 2005 (Box 28, Folder 15)
    - Jobs with Justice Healthcare for All, 2005-2006 (Box 28, Folder 16)
    - Jobs with Justice (old Jobs with Justice Pamphlets) Pamphlets, 2006 (Box 28, Folder 17)
    - Jobs with Justice Annual Strategic Planning, 2006 (Box 28, Folder 18)
    - Coalfield Religion - Labor Collaboration Strategy Meeting, 2006-11-15 (Box 28, Folder 19)
    - Jobs with Justice Meeting Organizational Challenges {Fred Azcarate}, 2006 (Box 28, Folder 20)
    - Jobs with Justice Women's Retreat, 2006 (Box 28, Folder 21)
    - U.S. Labor Against the War, 2006 (Box 28, Folder 22)
    - New Trade Union Initiative, 2006-10 (Box 28, Folder 23)
    - National Planning Committee Meeting - Atlanta, Georgia, 2006-12-19-2006-12-22 (Box 28, Folder 24)
    - United States Social Forum National Planning Committee, 2007 (Box 28, Folder 25)
    - United States Social Forum, 2007 (Box 28, Folder 26-27)
    - States Rights and International Trade Booklet, 2007 (Box 28, Folder 28)
    - United States Social Forum - Evaluation Team, 2007 (Box 28, Folder 29)
    - Social Security Administration No Match, 2007-12 (Box 28, Folder 30)
      Includes CD.
    - Asia Floor Wage Materials, 2007-2008 (Box 28, Folder 31)
    - Asia Floor Wage 6 Steps, 2007-2008 (Box 28, Folder 32)
    - Grassroots Global Justice, 2007-2009 (Box 28, Folder 33)
    - Jobs with Justice Strategic Growth Fund, 2008 (Box 28, Folder 34)
    - Signal Workers Campaign, 2008 (Box 28, Folder 35)
    - Grassroots Global Justice Coordinating Committee (CGJCC), 2008 (Box 28, Folder 36)
    - Grassroots Global Justice Strategic Plan, 2008 (Box 28, Folder 37)
    - Funders Network on Trade and Globalization, 2008 (Box 28, Folder 38)
    - Jobs with Justice In Person Local Coalition Meetings for Strategic Planning, 2008 (Box 28, Folder 39)
    - Low-Wage Immigrant Worker Coalition, 2008-02 (Box 28, Folder 40)
    - Grassroots Global Justice Coordinating Committee, 2008-03 (Box 28, Folder 41)
    - Grassroots Global Justice Documents, 2008 (Box 28, Folder 42)
    - Grassroots Global Justice, 2008 (Box 28, Folder 43)
    - Grassroots Global Justice Resource Mobilization, 2008-2009 (Box 28, Folder 44)
    - Jobs with Justice Implementation of Action Plan, 2009 (Box 28, Folder 45)
    - Grassroots Global Justice Mapping Money Report, 2009 (Box 28, Folder 46)
    - Inter-Alliance Dialogue, 2009 (Box 28, Folder 47)
    - Employee Free Choice Act, 2009 (Box 28, Folder 48)
    - Asian Floor Wage, Beijing, 2009-06-21-2009-06-22 (Box 28, Folder 49)
    - Asian Floor Wage - U.S. Campaign Development, 2009-10 (Box 28, Folder 50)
    - Economic Resources, 2010 (Box 28, Folder 51)
    - Inter-Alliance Dialogue/U.S. Social Forum, 2010 (Box 28, Folder 52)
    - Grassroots Global Justice Study, 2010 (Box 28, Folder 53)
    - Portland Jobs with Justice 20th Anniversary Booklet, 2011 (Box 28, Folder 54)
    - Jobs with Justice Pamphlets and Mailings, 2012 (Box 28, Folder 55)
    - Letter from United Mine Workers, 2016-09-22 (Box 28, Folder 56)
  - Training and Retreats
    - Jobs with Justice Economic Education, 1995-11 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Slide Show "Talking Points", 1996 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Staff Retreat, 1997-2002 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Building a More Powerful Movement for Justice "Labor-Community-Religious Coalition", 1997-1998 (Box 9, Folder 4-5)
    - Jobs with Justice Training, Orientation, 1998-2003 (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Women's Retreat, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 7-8)
    - Women's Retreat Follow Up, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - Training Curriculum, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - Jobs with Justice Staff Retreat/Annual Meeting, 2001-05-09 (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - Building Jobs with Justice Training, 2001-03 (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - Women's Retreat, 2002 (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - Women's Retreat Follow-Up, 2002 (Box 9, Folder 14)
    - Building Jobs with Justice Training, 2003 (Box 9, Folder 15-16)
    - Kentucky, 2003 (Box 9, Folder 17)
    - Federal Trade (FT) Retreats, 2003-07 (Box 9, Folder 18)
    - Staff Retreat, 2003-07 (Box 9, Folder 19)
    - Community Renewal Society-Organizing Training Evaluation Executive Summary, 2004 (Box 9, Folder 20)
    - New Trade Union Initiative Tour, 2004 (Box 9, Folder 21)
    - Workplace and Staff Meetings, 2004 (Box 9, Folder 22-23)
    - Staff and Leader Gathering, 2004 (Box 9, Folder 24)
    - Staff and Leader (SL) Gathering Applications, 2004 (Box 9, Folder 25)
    - Organizing and Collective Bargaining Rights Training Logistics, 2005 (Box 9, Folder 26)
    - Organizing and Collective Bargaining Rights Training, 2005-03-10-2005-03-13 (Box 9, Folder 27)
    - Field Retreats, 2005-11 (Box 9, Folder 28)
    - Midwest Academic Training, 2005-12-07-2005-12-09 (Box 9, Folder 29)
    - Organizing and Collective Bargaining Rights (OCBR) Training, 2005 (Box 9, Folder 30)
    - Good Jobs First, 2005-04 (Box 9, Folder 31)
    - Staff Retreat, 2006-01 (Box 9, Folder 32)
    - Women's Retreat, 2006 (Box 9, Folder 33)
    - Women's Retreat Logistics-Essentials, 2006 (Box 9, Folder 34)
    - Women's Retreat, 2006 (Box 9, Folder 35)
    - Women's Retreat, 2006-06 (Box 9, Folder 36)
    - Trainings, 2006-09 (Box 9, Folder 37)
    - Building Jobs with Justice, 2006-09 (Box 9, Folder 38)
    - Staff Retreat, 2003-07 (Box 9, Folder 39)
    - Trainings, 2007-2008 (Box 9, Folder 40)
    - Jobs with Justice, 2008-09 (Box 9, Folder 41)
  - Union Busting
    - Jackson Lewis Manual: How to Stay Union-Free into the 21st Century, 1999 (Box 54, Folder 33-35)
    - Jackson Lewis Manual (Copy 2), 1999 (Box 54, Folder 36-38)
    - Berman/Union Facts, 2006 (Box 54, Folder 39-40)
    - Berman Fact Sheets, 2006-08 (Box 54, Folder 41-42)
    - Richard Berman Deposition and Legal Documents, 2007-07 (Box 54, Folder 43)
    - Union Facts: Highlights of Philip Morris Documents, 2006-10-24 (Box 54, Folder 44)
    - The National Right to Work Committee and its Network Draft, 2005-08-05 (Box 54, Folder 45-46)
    - Washington-Baltimore News Guild Contract with Jobs with Justice-Education Fund, 2006-2018 (Box 54, Folder 47-48)
      Includes DVD.
  - Newsletters and Press
    - Newsletters, Mailings, and Monthly Updates
      - Early JWJ Newsletters, 1988-1990 (Box 3, Folder 1)
      - JWJ Newsletters, 1990-1991 (Box 3, Folder 2)
      - Coalition Mailings, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 3)
      - JWJ Newsletters, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 4)
      - JWJ Newsletters, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 5)
      - Coalition Mailings, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 6)
      - JWJ Newsletters, 1993-03 (Box 3, Folder 7)
      - Coalition Mailings, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 8)
      - JWJ Newsletters, 1994-1995 (Box 3, Folder 9)
      - Newsletters, 1995-10 (Box 3, Folder 10)
      - Coalition Mailings, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 11)
      - Newsletter, 1996-06-1996-12 (Box 3, Folder 12)
      - JWJ Press Releases, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 13)
      - Coalition Mailings, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 14)
      - JWJ Newsletters, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 15)
      - Coalition Mailings, 1997-01-08 (Box 3, Folder 16)
      - Feb Mailing, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 17)
      - March Mailing, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 18)
      - April Mailing, 1997-04 (Box 3, Folder 19)
      - Mailing, 1997-04 (Box 3, Folder 20)
      - May Mailing #2, 1997-05 (Box 3, Folder 21)
      - Mailing, 1997-05 (Box 3, Folder 22)
      - May Mailing, 1997-05 (Box 3, Folder 23)
      - June Mailing, 1997-06 (Box 3, Folder 24)
      - Mailing, 1997-07 (Box 3, Folder 25)
      - July Mailing, 1997-07 (Box 3, Folder 26)
      - Originals for August 1997 Mailing, 1997-08 (Box 3, Folder 27)
      - Originals - Sept., 1997-09 (Box 3, Folder 28)
      - JWJ Newsletters, 1997-2003 (Box 3, Folder 29)
      - January Mailing, 1998-01 (Box 3, Folder 30)
      - Labels - Feb Mailing, 1998-02 (Box 3, Folder 31)
      - February Monthly Mailing, 1998-02 (Box 3, Folder 32)
      - Feb + Jan, 1998-01-1998-02 (Box 3, Folder 33)
      - March Originals, 1998-03 (Box 3, Folder 34)
      - JWJ Newsletters, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 35)
      - April Mailing, 1998-04 (Box 3, Folder 36)
      - May Originals, 1998-05 (Box 3, Folder 37)
      - August Mailing Originals, 1998-08 (Box 4, Folder 1-2)
      - August Mailing, 1998-08 (Box 4, Folder 3)
      - September Mailing, 1998-09 (Box 4, Folder 4)
      - WRB Member Mailing, 1998-10 (Box 4, Folder 5)
      - October Mailing Originals, 1998-10 (Box 4, Folder 6)
      - November Mailing, 1998-11 (Box 4, Folder 7)
      - Originals, 1998-1999 (Box 4, Folder 8)
      - Haitian Nursing Home Workers, 1998-2000 (Box 4, Folder 9)
      - Winter Newsletter (Box 4, Folder 10)
      - Mailing, 1999-01 (Box 4, Folder 11)
      - Mailing, 1999-01 (Box 4, Folder 12)
      - Mailing, 1998-07 (Box 4, Folder 13)
      - WRB Member Mailing Originals, 1999-03 (Box 4, Folder 14)
      - March Mailing, 1999-03 (Box 4, Folder 15)
      - April Mailing, 1999-04 (Box 4, Folder 16)
      - May Mailing, 1999-05 (Box 4, Folder 17)
      - Monthly Mailing, 1999-06 (Box 4, Folder 18-19)
      - Mailing, 1999-08 (Box 4, Folder 20)
      - Sept Mailing, 1999-09 (Box 4, Folder 21)
      - Mailing, 1999-10 (Box 4, Folder 22)
      - Mailing, 1999-11 (Box 4, Folder 23)
      - Annual Meeting Follow Up Meeting, 2000-2001 (Box 4, Folder 24)
      - Mailing, 2000-01 (Box 4, Folder 25)
      - Mailing, 2000-02 (Box 4, Folder 26)
      - Mailing, 2000-03 (Box 4, Folder 27)
      - Mailing, 2000-04 (Box 4, Folder 28)
      - Mailing, 2000-09 (Box 4, Folder 29)
      - Mailing, 2000-08 (Box 4, Folder 30)
      - Mailing, 2000-10 (Box 4, Folder 31)
      - Mailing, 2000-11 (Box 4, Folder 32)
      - Mailing, 2001-01-2001-02 (Box 4, Folder 33)
      - Mailing, 2001-02 (Box 4, Folder 34)
      - Spring Newsletter (Box 4, Folder 35)
      - News Clips, 2001-05 (Box 5, Folder 1)
      - Press Release, 2001-07 (Box 5, Folder 2)
      - Mailing, 2001-08 (Box 5, Folder 3)
      - JWJ Update, 2001-10 (Box 5, Folder 4)
      - Mailing, 2001-11 (Box 5, Folder 5)
      - JWJ Update, 2001-12 (Box 5, Folder 6)
      - Update and Mailing, 2002-01 (Box 5, Folder 7)
      - Mailing, 2002-02 (Box 5, Folder 8)
      - Update and Press Clips, 2002-03 (Box 5, Folder 9)
      - Spring/Summer Newsletter (Box 5, Folder 10)
      - Update and Press Clips, 2002-05 (Box 5, Folder 11)
      - Mailing, 2002-06 (Box 5, Folder 12)
      - Update and Press Clips, 2002-07 (Box 5, Folder 13)
      - Update and Press Clips, 2002-08 (Box 5, Folder 14)
      - JWJ Update, 2002-09 (Box 5, Folder 15)
      - Newsletter, Fall 2002/Winter 2003 (Box 5, Folder 16)
      - Update and Press Clips, 2002-10 (Box 5, Folder 17)
      - Mailing, 2002-11 (Box 5, Folder 18)
      - Mailing, 2003-01 (Box 5, Folder 19)
      - It Takes a Community, 2003-03 (Box 5, Folder 20)
      - News Clips, 2003-04 (Box 5, Folder 21)
      - Update, 2003-05-2003-07 (Box 5, Folder 22)
      - Press Clips, 2003-08 (Box 5, Folder 23)
      - Update and Press Clips, 2003-09 (Box 5, Folder 24)
      - Mailing, 2003-11 (Box 5, Folder 25)
      - D10 Report, 2004-12-10 (Box 5, Folder 26)
      - Mailing, 2004-01 (Box 5, Folder 27)
      - Press Clips, 2004-01 (Box 5, Folder 28)
      - JWJ Update, 2004-03 (Box 5, Folder 29)
      - Update and Press Clips, 2004-04 (Box 5, Folder 30)
      - Mailing, 2004-05 (Box 5, Folder 31)
      - Update, 2004-06-2004-07 (Box 5, Folder 32)
      - Update, 2004-09-2004-10 (Box 5, Folder 33)
      - Newsletter, Winter (Box 5, Folder 34)
      - Update and Press Clips, 2005-01-2005-02 (Box 5, Folder 35)
      - Update and Press Clips, 2005-02 (Box 5, Folder 36)
      - Newsletter, Winter (Box 5, Folder 37)
    - Clippings
      - Miami, 1987 (Box 6, Folder 1)
      - Press Clips, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 2)
      - Press Clips, 1992 (Box 6, Folder 3)
      - Press Clips, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 4)
      - NLRB Action News Clips, 1993-05-27 (Box 6, Folder 5)
      - JWT Press Clips and Sound Policy, 1993-1995 (Box 6, Folder 6)
      - Oversize Clippings, 1993-1996 (Mapcase folder 2)
        Contains "Young Workers Unite" clipping from Boston Phoenix (September 6, 1996) and "Snapshot: May Day '93) from People's Weekly World (1993).
      - Press Clips, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 7)
      - Media Clips, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 8)
      - Press Clips, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 9)
      - Press Clips, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 10)
      - Press Clips, 1996 (Box 6, Folder 11)
      - Press Clips, 1996 (Box 6, Folder 12)
      - Press Clips, 1996 (Box 6, Folder 13)
      - JWJ Lexi's Search, 1996 (Box 6, Folder 14)
      - Press Clips/Photos, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 15)
      - Welfare DOA Press Clips, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 16)
      - Press Clips, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 17)
      - Oversize Clippings, 1999-2005 (Mapcase folder 1)
        Contains Dynamic: Magazine of the Young Communist League, USA (Spring-winter 2000), Venceremos: Chicana(o)/Latina(o) Student Newspaper (Vol. 5, No. 2, Spring 2000), AFT On Campus (Vol. 25, No.1, September 2005), JWJ Workers' Rights Board Hearing (Winter 2001), CWA News (Volume 59, Number 2, March 1999), Louisville Eccentric Observer (February 24, 1999).
      - Press Clips, 1998-1999 (Box 6, Folder 19)
      - Press Clips (Alphabetical by Paper), 2000-2001 (Box 6, Folder 20)
      - JWJ Press Materials, 2000-2001 (Box 6, Folder 21)
      - Press Clips, 2000-2002 (Box 6, Folder 22)
      - Clippings, 2000-2001 (Box 6, Folder 23)
      - FTAA Press Clips - Alphabetical by Paper, 2001 (Box 6, Folder 18)
      - Press Clips, 2001 (Box 6, Folder 24)
      - News Clippings, 2001 (Box 6, Folder 25)
      - Press Clippings, 2001-2002 (Box 6, Folder 26)
      - WSF/WEF Press Clips, 2002 (Box 6, Folder 27)
      - NWOM Press Clips, 2002-2003 (Box 6, Folder 28)
      - JWJ Press Clips, 2002-2006 (Box 6, Folder 29)
      - JWJ Press Clips, 2002-2006 (Box 6, Folder 30)
      - JWJ Year in Media - For Board, 2003 (Box 6, Folder 31)
      - GE Press Clips, 2003 (Box 6, Folder 32)
      - Clippings, 2004 (Box 6, Folder 33)
      - Miscellaneous Press Clips, 2004 (Box 6, Folder 34)
      - Economic Development, 2005 (Box 6, Folder 35)
      - Healthcare, 2005 (Box 6, Folder 36)
      - OCBR, 2005 (Box 6, Folder 37)
      - Immigrant Rights, 2005 (Box 38, Folder 1)
      - Immigrant Rights, 2005 (Box 38, Folder 2)
      - Global Justice, 2005 (Box 38, Folder 3)
      - Boston Globe, 2004-2006 (Box 38, Folder 4)
      - Chicago Tribune, 2005 (Box 38, Folder 5)
      - LA Times, 2004-2005 (Box 38, Folder 6)
      - NY Times, 2005 (Box 38, Folder 7)
      - Philadelphia Inquirer, 2005 (Box 38, Folder 8)
      - Washington Post, 2005 (Box 38, Folder 9)
      - Other, 2005 (Box 38, Folder 10)
      - Wires, 2005 (Box 38, Folder 11)
      - Columnists and Editors, 2005 (Box 38, Folder 12)
      - Regional Media Contacts, 2005 (Box 38, Folder 13)
      - Social Security, 2005 (Box 38, Folder 14)
      - Wal-Mart, 2005 (Box 38, Folder 15)
      - Wal-Mart, 2005 (Box 38, Folder 16)
      - Press Associates Union News Services News. Analysis, and Art for the Nation's Unions, 2005 (Box 38, Folder 17)
      - National Press, 2005 (Box 38, Folder 18)
      - National Press and Regional Press Economic Development, 2005 (Box 38, Folder 19)
      - National Press and Regional Press Immigration, Other, 2005 (Box 38, Folder 20)
      - National Regional Press Misc., 2005 (Box 38, Folder 21)
      - Clippings, 2005-01-2005-04 (Box 38, Folder 22)
      - Clippings, 2005-01-2005-04 (Box 38, Folder 23)
      - Clippings, 2005-05-2005-09 (Box 38, Folder 24)
      - Clippings, 2005-11-2005-12 (Box 38, Folder 25)
      - Regional Clippings, 2005-01-2005-04 (Box 38, Folder 26)
      - Regional Clippings, 2005-05-2005-07 (Box 38, Folder 27)
      - Regional Clippings, 2005-08-2005-12 (Box 38, Folder 28)
      - Regional Clippings, 2005-08-2005-12 (Box 38, Folder 29)
      - Unsolicited Media Hits, 2005-2006 (Box 38, Folder 30)
      - Press Items About Labor I, 2005-2011 (Box 38, Folder 31)
      - Press Items About Labor I, 2005-2011 (Box 38, Folder 32)
      - National Press and Regional Healthcare Press, 2005-2006 (Box 38, Folder 33)
      - Press Items about Labor II, 2006 (Box 38, Folder 34)
      - National Press I, 2006 (Box 38, Folder 35)
      - National Press and Regional Press, 2006 (Box 38, Folder 36)
      - Clippings, 2006 (Box 38, Folder 37)
      - Unsolicited Media Call Intake Forms, 2006-05 (Box 38, Folder 38)
      - Pitch Response Forms, 2006 (Box 38, Folder 39)
      - Newspaper Clippings, 2008 (Box 38, Folder 40)
      - Press Clips, 2012 (Box 38, Folder 41)
      - Press Clips, 2012 (Box 38, Folder 42)
      - Press Clips, 2013 (Box 38, Folder 43)
- Series II. Regional Coalitions
  - Campaigns/Budget/Fundraisers, 2015 (Box 51, Folder 4)
  - Puerto Rico, 1999-04-14 (Box 51, Folder 9)
  - Jobs with Justice - New Zealand, 1998 (Box 51, Folder 10)
  - Local Planning Retreats, 1996-2000 (Box 51, Folder 11)
  - Local Coalitions Survey, 1991 (Box 51, Folder 12)
  - Local Coalition Building, 1991 (Box 51, Folder 13)
  - Local Coalition Building, 1991-1992 (Box 51, Folder 14)
  - Local Coalition Building, 1993 (Box 51, Folder 15)
  - Local Coalitions Survey, 1993 (Box 51, Folder 16)
  - JWJ Local Coalition Reports, 1996-02-27 (Box 51, Folder 17)
  - Local Coalition Contacts, 1996 (Box 51, Folder 18)
  - Local Coalition Calls, 1997 (Box 51, Folder 19)
  - JWJ Starter Kit, 1995 (Box 52, Folder 57)
  - Mid-West Coalitions
    - Justice for Janitors Midwest, 2005-2006 (Box 51, Folder 50)
    - Midwest Work Plans and Coalition Reports, 2006 (Box 51, Folder 52)
    - Midwest Coalition Development Goals, 2005 (Box 51, Folder 53)
    - Public Employee CB, 2005 (Box 51, Folder 54)
    - Ohio
      - Ohio State, 2007-2009 (Box 44, Folder 3-4)
      - Cleveland JWJ, 2000-2001 (Box 36, Folder 13-17)
      - Cleveland Planning Retreat, 2000-2001 (Box 36, Folder 18)
      - Cleveland WRB, 2001 (Box 36, Folder 19)
      - Cleveland JWJ Workers Rights Board, 1994-2000 (Box 36, Folder 20-22)
      - Cleveland JWJ, 1999-2000 (Box 43, Folder 1)
      - Cleveland, OH '00, 2000 (Box 43, Folder 2- 3)
      - Cleveland $$, 2003-2004 (Box 43, Folder 4)
      - CLE, 2002-04-23-2002-05-14 (Box 43, Folder 5)
      - Cleveland, OH 97-98, 1997-1998 (Box 43, Folder 6-8)
      - Cleveland JWJ, 1996 (Box 43, Folder 9)
      - Cleveland, OH, 1994-2000 (Box 43, Folder 10-11)
      - CLE, 2011 (Box 43, Folder 12)
      - USSF, 2009-2010 (Box 43, Folder 13)
      - Cleveland Jobs with Justice, 2008-2009 (Box 43, Folder 14)
      - Cleveland, 2004 (Box 43, Folder 15)
      - Cleveland Jobs with Justice Strategic Retreat, 2004 (Box 43, Folder 16)
      - Cleveland HCOP, 2002-2004 (Box 43, Folder 17)
      - Cleveland Staff Search, 2004 (Box 43, Folder 18)
      - Susan Hagan, 2003-2004 (Box 43, Folder 19)
      - Cleveland, 2002-2003 (Box 43, Folder 20)
      - Cleveland JWJ, 1999 (Box 43, Folder 21-22)
      - Cleveland, 2006-2009 (Box 43, Folder 23)
      - Cleveland, OH, 1999 (Box 43, Folder 39)
      - Cleveland, 2002-2003 (Box 52, Folder 54)
      - Lorain JWJ, 1994-11-23-1995-05-11 (Box 43, Folder 24)
      - Youngstown, OH JWJ (possible), 1996-11-09-2001-08-01 (Box 43, Folder 25)
      - OH Database, 2001 (Box 43, Folder 26)
      - Toledo, 2003-2005 (Box 43, Folder 27)
      - Toledo, 2006-2008 (Box 43, Folder 28)
      - Jobs with Justice Toledo, 2008-10-14-2008-12-03 (Box 43, Folder 29)
      - Columbus, 2002-02-27 (Box 43, Folder 30)
      - Columbus, 2003-2004 (Box 43, Folder 31-32)
      - Columbus, 2006-2007 (Box 43, Folder 33)
      - Columbus + Cleveland, 2001-2006 (Box 43, Folder 34-35)
      - Tri-Mahoning Valley JWJ, 2001 (Box 43, Folder 36)
      - Mahoning Valley, 2001-2003 (Box 43, Folder 37)
      - Columbia, OH, 1999-05-27 (Box 43, Folder 38)
      - Columbia, OH, 1994-1999 (Box 43, Folder 40)
      - Columbia JWJ, 1999-2000 (Box 43, Folder 41)
      - Miami Valley, 2008-2010 (Box 43, Folder 42)
      - Miami Valley JWJ, 2007-2009 (Box 44, Folder 1-2)
    - Illinois
      - Chicago JWJ, 2007-2010 (Box 44, Folder 5-7)
      - FBOP Chicago, 2005 (Box 44, Folder 8)
      - Champaign-Urbana, 2005-2006 (Box 44, Folder 9)
      - Chicago: WRB, 1997 (Box 44, Folder 10)
      - Chicago Illinois, 1996-1998 (Box 44, Folder 11-12)
      - Chicago WRB Hearing, 1999 (Box 44, Folder 13)
      - Chicago Illinois, 2001 (Box 44, Folder 14)
      - Chicago, 1998-2002 (Box 44, Folder 15)
      - Chicago JWJ, 2001 (Box 44, Folder 16)
      - Chicago JWJ, 2000 (Box 44, Folder 17)
      - Chicago May Day protests, Press Clips, Other '00 Actions + Materials, 2000 (Box 44, Folder 18)
      - Chicago, 1999 (Box 44, Folder 19)
      - Chicago, 1999-2003 (Box 44, Folder 20-22)
      - Chicago Staff, 2002-2005 (Box 44, Folder 23-24)
      - Chicago, 2004 (Box 44, Folder 25-26)
      - Chicago $$, 2004 (Box 44, Folder 27-28)
      - Chicago HCOP, 2002-2003 (Box 44, Folder 29)
    - Indiana
      - Tri-State Evansville Charter App., 2011 (Box 44, Folder 30)
      - NW Indiana, 2008-2009 (Box 44, Folder 31)
      - Indianapolis, 2006-2009 (Box 44, Folder 33)
      - Indianapolis JWJ, 2004 (Box 44, Folder 51)
      - Indianapolis JWJ, 2001 (Box 44, Folder 42)
      - Indianapolis JWJ, 2000 (Box 44, Folder 43)
      - Indianapolis, 2000-2003 (Box 44, Folder 49)
      - Bloomington/South Central Indiana, 2005-2007 (Box 44, Folder 34)
      - Bloomington, 2001 (Box 44, Folder 37)
      - Bloomington, 1999 (Box 44, Folder 38)
      - Bloomington JWJ, 1997-1998 (Box 44, Folder 39)
      - Bloomington JWJ, 1995-2000 (Box 44, Folder 40)
      - Bloomington, 2001-06-04-2002-01-21 (Box 44, Folder 41)
      - Bloomington JWJ, 2000 (Box 44, Folder 44)
      - Bloomington JWJ, 2000 (Box 44, Folder 45)
      - Calumet Project for Industrial Jobs, 2000 (Box 44, Folder 46)
      - Indiana, 1999 (Box 44, Folder 47)
      - St. Joseph Valley Project, 2001 (Box 44, Folder 48)
        floppy disc
      - St. Joe Valley, 2009 (Box 44, Folder 35)
      - St. Joseph/South Bend, 2002-2003 (Box 44, Folder 36)
      - S. Bend, 2006 (Box 44, Folder 32)
      - S. Bend, 2003-2004 (Box 44, Folder 50)
    - Iowa
      - Iowa, 1998-11-10-1998-12-30 (Box 44, Folder 52)
    - Missouri
      - Kansas City, MO, 2006-2007 (Box 36, Folder 1)
      - St. Louis, 2006 (Box 36, Folder 2)
      - St. Louis Fundraising, 2002-2004 (Box 36, Folder 3)
      - St. Louis, 2004 (Box 36, Folder 4)
      - St. Louis Electoral, 2004 (Box 36, Folder 5)
      - St. Louis HCOP, 2002-2003 (Box 36, Folder 6)
      - St. Louis JWJ, 2001 (Box 36, Folder 7)
      - St. Louis, 2002-2003 (Box 36, Folder 8)
      - St. Louis, MO, 1997-1998 (Box 36, Folder 9)
      - St. Louis, MO, 2001 (Box 36, Folder 10)
      - St. Louis, MO JWJ, 1994-1995 (Box 36, Folder 11)
    - Nebraska
      - Omaha, 2002 (Box 36, Folder 12)
    - Michigan
      - TOFF, 2008-2009 (Box 36, Folder 23)
      - Detroit JWJ, 1997-2003 (Box 36, Folder 24)
      - Detroit, 2004 (Box 36, Folder 25)
      - Detroit, 2001-2003 (Box 36, Folder 26)
      - Detroit WRB, 2001 (Box 36, Folder 27)
      - Detroit, 2001 (Box 36, Folder 28)
      - Detroit, 1999 (Box 36, Folder 29)
      - Kalamazoo, 1999 (Box 36, Folder 30)
      - Michigan JWJ, 1993-2001 (Box 36, Folder 31)
    - Wisconsin
      - Turn Around America: AFL-CIO Midwest Regional Conference, 2009 (Box 36, Folder 32-33)
      - WI JWJ, 2001 (Box 36, Folder 34)
      - Milwaukee, WI, 1999 (Box 36, Folder 35)
      - Milwaukee, WI, 1997-1998 (Box 36, Folder 36)
      - Milwaukee: WRB, 1997 (Box 36, Folder 37-38)
      - Milwaukee, 2001-2002 (Box 36, Folder 39)